The rules of the Heavenly Dao are so tyrannical.
The life and death of all things are strictly bound by it.
For cultivators like us,
what room is there left for choice?
Do not speak nonsense.
The ways of this world
were established only after enduring thousands of tribulations.
It is not for you to casually judge right from wrong.
High God,
have you never doubted the Heavenly Dao?
Never.
Come.
Drink this tea.
If becoming an immortal means cutting off all emotions,
then I'd rather be reverted to my original form.
Among these emotions,
who exactly is it that you cannot forget?
I'm afraid
of forgetting the longing in my heart.
To me,
on this lonely, difficult,
centuries-long path of cultivation,
he is exceptionally precious.
Drink it.
I will help you keep this longing.
Drink it now.
Thank you, Immortal.
Go.
Deity.
Break.
Your reaction shows you clearly know her.
I know her.
What happened to her?
Ancestor, this is the mortal realm.
There's no shame in romance.
Nonsense.
Get to the point.
A century after you descended to the mortal realm,
which is just a few years in the immortal realm.
Bai Jingqing
voluntarily resigned her immortal post and came to the mortal realm.
Why would she want to start over?
Everything is predestined.
This was her choice
and her karma.
Ancestor.
I think
that is her karma.
At that time,
it was indeed my fault.
An immortal should not be moved by pity.
But all things in the past
are gone.
What does this have to do with Feilu?
This Feilu
is the reincarnation of Bai Jingqing.
I understand.
You may leave.
Then, Ancestor,
I will take my leave.
Greetings, immortal friend.
I am Baili Lingfeng,
and my duty is to guard the Zhexian Terrace.
People often say that destiny makes fools of men.
I know a little bit about
the reason for your departure.
If you are trying to persuade me,
then save your breath.
Immortal friend.
High God Qingxuan,
formed from a single thought over ten thousand years,
took shape from that thought.
His Dao heart is extremely resolute,
as indestructible as a diamond.
And he has guarded the Sanshan Stream in the Heaven Realm for tens of thousands of years.
His actions and thoughts have their own Dao to follow.
But if you leave this time,
won't it be a tribulation for you?
I remind you,
if you descend to the mortal realm,
you will lose all your memories
and all your magical powers.
Whether you become a human or a beast
is yet unknown.
High God Qingxuan.
You know him?
We just have some ties of destiny.
Where is he now?
If it's meant to be,
you will definitely meet.
Xiaoxiao.
He looks exactly like you.
Good boy.
Your name will be Feilu.
Chen Feilu.
Feilu.
Good name.
Why did it change back?
The talisman isn't working.
Didn't the master say his goods are genuine?
What are you looking at,
Master?
Pingjie Qianghaihui.